===========================================================================================================================================================================================

**Graham Media Group Privacy Policy**
=====================================

### Last Updated: June 28, 2024

#### Introduction

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) explains how and why [Graham Media Group](https://www.grahammedia.com/) and its business units, subsidiaries, and other affiliated entities (collectively referred to herein as “Graham Media Group”, “GMG”, “we”, “us” or “our”) with websites where this Policy is posted collect, store, use, disclose, share, or otherwise process your personal information. We take user privacy seriously and are committed to protecting it as described in this Privacy Policy.

GMG entities to which this Policy applies include, but are not limited to, the following seven local media hubs:

* [KPRC (Houston, TX)](https://www.click2houston.com/);
    
* [KSAT (San Antonio, TX)](https://www.ksat.com/);
    
* [WDIV (Detroit, MI)](https://www.clickondetroit.com/);
    
* [WKMG (Orlando, FL)](https://www.clickorlando.com/);
    
* [WJXT/WCWJ (Jacksonville, FL)](https://www.news4jax.com/);
    
* [WSLS (Roanoke, VA)](https://www.wsls.com/);

plus [Solutionaries](https://www.solutionariesnetwork.com/) and [Omne Results](https://omneresults.com/). Please note that this policy does not apply to GMG Social News Desk (a separate Privacy Policy for Social News Desk is available [here](https://www.socialnewsdesk.com/privacy-policy/)). You can learn more about Graham Media Group by visiting [https://www.grahammedia.com/](https://www.grahammedia.com/).

The section titled “[Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions](https://www.grahammedia.com/privacy-policy/#jurisdictions)” below provides information about our compliance with applicable U.S. state privacy laws (“Applicable Privacy Laws”).

o   If you are a resident of California, the “[California Notice at Collection](https://www.grahammedia.com/privacy-policy/#californianotice)” and “[Additional Disclosures for California Residents](https://www.grahammedia.com/privacy-policy/#californiaresidents)” subsections contain further information about our handling of your data and your data subject rights. 

o   If you are a non-California resident the subsection below titled, “[Additional Information for Residents of States with Applicable Privacy Laws](https://www.grahammedia.com/privacy-policy/#additionalinfo)” includes information about privacy rights you may have under other state privacy laws.

#### Table of Contents

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy in its entirety, but you can navigate to specific areas using the links below:

#### General

Unless varied by the terms or privacy policy posted on a particular website or provided to you as part of your relationship with GMG, the privacy practices described below apply to all personal information collected by GMG. This includes information collected through any websites, mobile applications, widgets, tools, features, and content (including videos and images) that we may offer or employ on any platform (collectively, the “Services”) that is owned or managed by GMG. This policy does not apply to information collected by third parties, including through any platform or content that may link to or be accessible from any of our websites.

Included below is an overview of our approach to privacy:

* We collect information about you to provide you with the best experience using our media platforms or accessing other Services we provide.
    
* We do not make money by selling your information to third parties.
    
* We only give third-parties access to your information when it is necessary to provide you with the Services we make available or because you have asked us to do so.

You have choices with how we use the information we collect and maintain about you and can ask us to update or remove that information at any time.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made part of the [Terms of Use](https://www.grahammedia.com/terms/) which govern your use of the Services we provide.

#### Information We Collect

While legal definitions of personal information or personal data can vary in different jurisdictions, we consider “personal information” to be any information that identifies you as an individual or is directly linkable to you as an identifiable individual. Not all information we collect is personal information under this definition. For example, information that has been de-identified or aggregated in a way that no longer allows identification of a particular person would not meet this definition. Similarly, information we gather about you from publicly available sources, such as government databases, may not be considered personal information in your jurisdiction. Where permitted, we may combine personal information that you have given us with publicly available information about you to create a profile about you, your interests, and your preferences that helps us personalize your experience of the Services.

We may collect, store, and process personal information from various categories. These categories include:

* **Identifiers**: This may include your name, address, physical telephone number; email address, and date of birth.
    
* **Demographic information**: This may include your gender and/or age.
    
* **Internet or other electronic network activity:** This may include browsing information, site navigation data, referring source (including referring URLs), exit URL, browser type, browser identifier, IP address and other similar information collected via cookies and other online tracking technologies.
    
* **Audio, visual, or similar information:** This may include photos, videos or other recordings you choose to share with us.
    
* **Geolocation data**: This may include geolocation data from your computer or phone (e.g., to provide live weather radar maps).
    
* **Commercial information**: This may include records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, payment methods, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
    
* **Inferences**: This may include profiles created about you that reflect your interests and preferences.

**Our listing of these categories does not mean that all categories or examples listed in each category are collected about everyone who uses the Services. We are providing a complete list in the spirit of transparency.**

We collect this information:

* Directly from you when you provide it to us, for example, by signing up for an Insider account, submitting an inquiry or comment to us online or via email, or providing us with your contact information to receive news and weather alerts.
    
* We may supplement the information you provide directly with information received or otherwise obtained from third parties. This information may be received or obtained from our partners in sponsored content sections of the Services or from other third parties who provide us with user group and audience data they have compiled based on factors such as age, gender, geography, interests, and online activity. For example, we may receive information about you from a social media site if you connect to the Services through that site.
    
* Automatically when you visit or use our Services or interact with us in other ways through cookies (small text files containing a string of characters sent to your computer) and similar tracking technologies (such as web beacons or pixels) that tell us which pages were visited and by how many users, the order in which pages were visited, and which hyperlinks were “clicked.” Not all of this information is personal information, as we define it above. Information collected by these technologies can be necessary for site navigation and performance or, in some instances, used by our business partners or us for targeted advertising purposes.

* Certain of our sites employ a tool from data-privacy software provider [Osano](https://protect-us.mimecast.com/s/57zmCVOr91u2mOw2Sz9nVJ?domain=osano.com/ "https://www.osano.com/") that allows you to customize your cookie preferences. Where we make that tool available, you can access it to change your preferences anytime by clicking the Cookie Preferences link located at the bottom of any of our web pages. The tool will record when you have acknowledged our use of cookies and will periodically prompt you to consider your choices to ensure you stay up to date with changes to our privacy practices. The tool controls the marketing and analytical cookies set by using the Services. Essential cookies cannot be disabled from the cookies tool. All users may have additional options to control how and whether cookies and similar technologies will be accepted through settings available from your chosen web browser. For more information on how to change these settings, please refer to your browser help menu. Be aware that if you choose to disable cookies at the web browser level, some features of the Services may not function properly or be accessible to you.

The Services may contain links to other websites, including the websites of our sponsors and partners. These third-party websites may collect information directly from you or set cookies or other tracking tools on your device. We are not responsible for the privacy practices these third parties employ when you visit their websites. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content received from a third party, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

#### How We Use the Information Collected

The specific local media hub or other GMG entity that collects your personal information will generally be the primary user of information collected from you. This includes using that information on Services that might be on different platforms than the platform through which the information was initially provided. Other GMG entities may access your information where they perform services on behalf of the collecting entity, unless prohibited under applicable law, for use on their behalf for the purposes described in this privacy policy. Consistent with applicable law and the choices and controls that may be available to you, we may use information collected from you or from devices associated with you as follows:

* _To Provide and Manage the Products and Services You Request_. This includes, for example, creating and maintaining your local media Insider account, processing your subscription, sending you confirmation notices regarding services you have requested, delivering localized weather and news alerts consistent with your choices, and notifying contest or sweepstakes winners. This may also include using your personal information to personalize and improve your experience on our Services.
    
* _To Contact You_. We may periodically contact you with information about upcoming events and programs or other content that might interest you. You may opt out of receiving commercial email messages from us by following the instructions contained in those email messages.
    
* _To Better Understand Our Users and Improve Our Services_. We may collect information on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior and analyze that data. We do this to better understand and serve our users and to improve our products and Services.
    
* _To Deliver Targeted Advertising_. We may use your information, including your location information, to facilitate the delivery of targeted ads, promotions, and offers to you, on behalf of ourselves and advertisers, on and off the Services.
    
* _To Protect the Services and the Rights of Users and Others_. We may use your personal information as we believe is necessary or appropriate to protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, and safety of property displayed on the Services, our employees or agents, or other users, and comply with applicable law.
    
* _In Limited Circumstances With Your Consent_. We may obtain your consent to process personal information for other specified purposes.
    
* _To Comply with Legal Obligations, Resolve Disputes and Enforce Agreements_. For example, to notify you regarding any concerns with the Services, including, as required by law, if personal information you provided to us is exposed to unauthorized third parties.

When we sponsor promotions or sweepstakes, or third parties’ sponsor promotions or sweepstakes in conjunction with us, either the third party or we will post any additional relevant privacy information in the official rules and/or registration area for the promotion or sweepstakes. To the extent it conflicts with this Privacy Policy, that privacy information will govern that promotion or sweepstakes.

#### How We Share Your Information

The categories of personal information that we may have shared for a business or commercial purpose include any of the categories of personal information shown in the Information We Collect section of this Privacy Policy.

**_We process certain categories of personal information for purposes of targeted advertising. Those include identifiers, demographic information, Internet browsing or other electronic network activity information, geolocation data, and inferences drawn from the above. We may share these categories of personal information with our affiliates, business partners, and certain service providers. You may opt out of this type of sharing by using the form here:_** 

Select Your Station - Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information Form KPRC (Houston, TX) KSAT (San Antonio, TX) WDIV (Detroit, MI) WJXT (Jacksonville, FL) WKMG (Orlando, FL) WSLS (Roanoke, VA)

The parties with whom we may share personal information are:

* _Affiliates_. We may share information within GMG.
    
* _Business Partners_. We may also share information with business partners to provide you with the Services you request. For example, if you choose to enter a contest or sweepstakes that we are hosting with third parties, we may provide your information to those third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these entities.
    
* _Service Providers_. We may share information with and receive information from companies providing services on our behalf, such as advertising service providers, website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, payment processing companies, and other similar vendors and services providers. We will not authorize these third parties to use your personal information except as necessary to provide services to us or for purposes authorized by us. [Hearken](https://wearehearken.com/) is a third-party service provider.
    
* _Social Media Sites and Other Similar Platforms_. When you direct us to share your personal information with or link the Services to third-party sites or platforms, such as social media sites, we will comply with that request. Please note that once we share your personal information with another company in this circumstance, the information received by the other company is controlled by that company and becomes subject to their privacy practices.
    
* _Information Posted to Public Forums_. The Services may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups, and/or other similar features available to users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution when disclosing personal information about you or anyone else in such a forum. GMG does not accept responsibility for ensuring the privacy of any information you choose to disclose in these areas. Any content or information you provide to these areas of the Services is done at your own risk.
    
* _Other Parties When Required or Permitted by Law, or As Necessary to Protect Our Users and Services_. We may use and share your personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to protect the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of GMG, our employees, or users, to detect, suppress or prevent fraud, or where otherwise required or permitted by law or legal process, including responding to requests from public authorities.
    
* _Other Parties in Connection With a Corporate Transaction_. We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you if we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party, such as in the event of a merger, acquisition, or in connection with a bankruptcy reorganization.

We may use information, including personal information, we have collected about you to create de-identified and/or aggregated data sets, such as de-identified demographic information, aggregated trends, reports, or statistics about how users interact with the Services. De-identified and aggregated information is used for various functions, including measuring visitors’ interest in and use of various portions or features of the Services we offer. Such de-identified and aggregated information does not identify you individually and is, therefore, not personal information for purposes of this Privacy Policy. We may disclose such de-identified or aggregated information in several ways, including to improve the Services, for our internal business purposes, and any other legally permissible purpose.

#### How We Protect Your Information

We take the security of your personal information seriously. We implement commercially reasonable technical, physical, and administrative security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction of personal information collected through the Services.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We cannot and do not guarantee that your personal information will never be accessed by an unauthorized party or otherwise breached during transmission through the Internet. Additionally, any contact with us by email or through the Services might not be secure. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on our websites.

If we believe the information you provided to us has been exposed to unauthorized third parties, we will notify you as required by law or upon our own choice. In the event of such unauthorized exposure, we expressly reserve the right to provide notice to you electronically via any email address you have provided if permitted by law. If you have reason to believe that your personal information, including any password you created for access to the Services, is no longer secure, please notify us immediately by contacting us via one of the methods listed below.

#### Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions

Residents of certain states have additional rights under applicable privacy laws, as described in this section. If you are a resident of California, please review our “California Notice at Collection” provided directly below. The following subsection includes additional information about your privacy rights under applicable California privacy laws.

If you are a resident of another state that has enacted an applicable privacy law, please review the subsection entitled “Additional Information for Residents of States with Applicable Privacy Laws” below for additional information about your privacy rights under applicable state privacy laws.

**California Notice at Collection**

This California Notice at Collection (the “Notice”) provides California residents with information about our collection, use, and disclosure of their personal information. Please reference the other sections of the Privacy Policy for more information about our privacy practices.

This Notice is provided pursuant to the California Consumer Privacy Act, as modified by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020 (the “CCPA”), supplements and should be read in conjunction with this Policy. The information in this section applies solely to consumers who reside in the State of California.

**_Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information_**

The chart below describes how and why we collect, use, and disclose personal information. It also describes how and why we have collected, used, and disclosed personal information within the past 12 months.

| **Category** | **Examples** | **Purpose, Use, and/or Disclosure of Personal Information** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers | This may include your name, address, physical telephone number, email address, and date of birth. | · To provide and manage our products and Services. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>To send you information, including targeted advertisements, about new promotions, products, and services offered by GMG and our selected partners. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To create and maintain an account.  <br>· To comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce agreements.  <br>· To contact you, this may include providing information related to accounts and services, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and administrative messages.  <br>· To carry out other specific disclosed purposes that you have consented to. |
| Demographic information | This may include your gender and/or age. Please note that these are characteristics of protected classifications under California law. | · To comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce agreements.  <br>· To personalize and improve your experience on our Services. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To send you information, including targeted advertisements, about new promotions, products, and services offered by GMG and our selected partners. In some instances, we may disclose non-sensitive demographic information to third parties for this purpose. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | This may include browsing information, site navigation data, referring source (including referring URLs), exit URL, browser type, browser identifier, IP address and other similar information collected via cookies and other online tracking technologies. | · To diagnose problems with our websites and to improve, upgrade or enhance the websites and our Services. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To personalize and improve your experience on our websites. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To analyze the performance of promotional efforts. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To send you information, including targeted advertisements, about new promotions, products, and services offered by GMG and our selected partners. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To provide and manage our products and Services. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose. |
| Audio, visual, or similar information | This may include photos, videos or other recordings you choose to share with us. | · To provide and manage our products and Services.  <br>· To carry out other specific disclosed purposes that you have consented to. |
| Geolocation data | This may include geolocation data from your computer or phone (e.g., to provide live weather radar maps).  <br>  <br>In some instances, this data may be precise enough to constitute “sensitive personal information”; however, this data is not used for purposes of inferring characteristics about you. | · To personalize and improve your experience on our Services. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To provide and manage our products and Services. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To carry out other specific disclosed purposes that you have consented to. |
| Commercial information | This may include records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, payment methods, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | · To comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce agreements.  <br>· To create and maintain an account.  <br>· To provide and manage our products and Services. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To carry out other specific disclosed purposes that you have consented to. |
| Inferences drawn from other information | This may include profiles created about you that reflects your interests, and preferences. | · To personalize and improve your experience on our websites.  <br>· To personalize and improve your experience on our Services. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To send you information, including targeted advertisements, about new promotions, products, and services offered by GMG and our selected partners. In some instances, we disclose this information to third parties for this purpose.  <br>· To carry out other specific disclosed purposes that you have consented to. |

**_Selling and Sharing of Personal Information_**

GMG does not “sell” personal information, nor do we have actual knowledge of any “sale” of personal information of minors under 16 years of age. That said, we may share information with third-party advertising partners for the purpose of promoting our Services as described above, such as for targeted advertising.

We may share the following categories of data with advertising partners for this purpose: 

* Identifiers,
    
* Inferences,
    
* Demographic Information, and
    
* Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity.

To the extent that such sharing is considered a “sale”, "sharing", or "targeted advertising" under applicable state law, you may limit such sharing by following the instructions found below in the section titled “Exercising Your Rights” or by contacting us as set forth in the “How to Contact Us” section below. You may also opt-out by visiting our “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information” page:

Select Your Station - Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information Form KPRC (Houston, TX) KSAT (San Antonio, TX) WDIV (Detroit, MI) WJXT (Jacksonville, FL) WKMG (Orlando, FL) WSLS (Roanoke, VA)

**_Retention of Personal Information_**

We will retain your personal information collected pursuant to this privacy policy for as long as we deem reasonably necessary or desirable for our and our business customers’ legitimate business purposes, unless a different retention period is required by any applicable law, rule or regulation. We reserve the right to delete or destroy any information collected, including personal information, at any time.

**Additional Disclosures for California Residents**

The categories of and the sources from which we collect personal information vary based on our relationship or interaction with a specific California resident and the business purpose for which the personal information is collected. Please reference the “Information We Collect” and “How We Use the Information Collected” sections for more information about these practices. Details regarding how we may share your personal information is available in the “How We Share Your Information” section above.

**California Consumer Rights**

Subject to certain exceptions, as a California resident, you have the following rights to your personal information:

**_Right to Know and Access_**: Request access to your personal information that we have collected, used, disclosed, or sold about you, including:

* The categories of personal information we have collected about you, including:

o   The categories of sources from which the personal information was collected;

o   Our business or commercial purposes for collecting or disclosing personal information;

o   The categories of recipients to which we disclose personal information; and

o   The categories of personal information that we disclosed for a business purpose, and for each category identified, the categories of recipients to which we disclosed that particular category of personal information; or

* The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.

**_Right to Deletion_:** Request deletion of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain limitations. If you ask to delete your personal information, we will respect your request and delete your personal information, subject to certain exceptions provided by law, such as but not limited to:

* Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our contract with you.
    
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
    
* Exercise free speech, to ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law.
    
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code 1546 seq.).
    
* Comply with a legal obligation.
    
* Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.

**_Right to Correction_:** You have the right to request that we correct personal information we maintain about you that you believe is inaccurate.

**_Right to Opt-out of Sales and Sharing_:** You have the right to opt-out of your personal information being shared for purposes of targeted advertising.

**_Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal information_**: We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information in any way that is governed by the CCPA.

**_Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of Rights_:** You have the right to be free from unlawful discrimination for exercising your rights under the CCPA. We will not discriminate against you based upon your exercising your rights with respect to your personal information.

**_Exercising Your Rights_**

If you are a California resident and wish to exercise any of these rights, you can contact us by completing this form:

Select Your Station - Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information Form KPRC (Houston, TX) KSAT (San Antonio, TX) WDIV (Detroit, MI) WJXT (Jacksonville, FL) WKMG (Orlando, FL) WSLS (Roanoke, VA)

or by calling us at (833) 971-2464.

When submitting your request, you must provide sufficient information that allows us to verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or their authorized agent. This information includes your first and last name and email address. When submitting your request, please provide sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate and respond to the request. We will only use personal information provided in your request to verify your identity or authority to make the request. If we cannot verify your identity from the information already maintained by us, we may request that you provide additional information for the purposes of verifying your identity and for security or fraud prevention purposes. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm that the personal information relates to you.

**_Authorized Agents_**.

You may designate an authorized agent to make requests on your behalf. We will require verification that you did in fact give that person your authorization. Unless the law requires otherwise, your authorized agent must provide contact details for you. We will contact you to confirm that you authorized the agent to act on your behalf. Once you confirm, we will promptly respond to the rights request. Please note, we will not share information about a business customer with anyone not clearly affiliated with that business.

**_Response Timing_**

We will attempt to respond to a verifiable consumer request within 45 days of its receipt. If we require more time, we will inform you of the reason and the necessary extension period in writing.

**_Verification Process_**

We may request that you provide additional information reasonably necessary to verify you and your consumer’s request. If you submit the request through an authorized agent, we may need to collect additional information to verify your identify before processing your request. If you are using an authorized agent to exercise your rights, we may deny a request if the authorized agent does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf.

**Additional Information for Residents of States with Applicable Privacy Laws**

Residents of certain U.S. states other than California have the right to receive disclosures regarding a business’ processing of “personal data”, as defined under Applicable Privacy Law. Residents of these states may have unique rights with respect to our processing of such personal data. To the extent you are a resident of a state with such a privacy law, and we collect, use or disclose personal data subject to your state’s privacy law, this section of our Policy applies. For more information about the personal data we collect, use and disclose, please see “Information We Collect,” “How We Use Information Collected,” and “How We Share Your Information” sections in this Policy.

**_Consumer Rights_**

Under Applicable Privacy Law, you have the following rights:

* **_Right to Access_:** You have the right to confirm whether or not we are processing your personal data and to access such personal data. 
    
* **_Right of Portability_:** You may have the right to obtain a copy of the personal data that you previously provided to us in a format of our choosing as long as it is accessible and machine readable.
    
* **_Right to Delete_:** You have the right to ask us to delete certain personal data we have collected about you. 
    
* **_Right to Correction_:** You have the right to ask us to correct inaccuracies in the personal data we have collected. 
    
* **_Right to Opt-out of Sale_:** A “sale” includes disclosing or making available personal data to a third party in exchange for money. We do not “sell” personal data as defined under Applicable Privacy Laws; thus, this right is not available consumers at this time. 
    
* **_Right to Opt-out of Targeted Advertising_**: You have the right to opt out of the processing of your personal data if it is used for targeted advertising. Applicable state privacy laws may provide the right to opt out of the processing of personal data for decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning you.

**_Exercising Your Rights_**

If you are a resident of a state that has enacted a comprehensive privacy law and wish to exercise any of these rights, you can contact us by completing this form:

Select Your Station - Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information Form KPRC (Houston, TX) KSAT (San Antonio, TX) WDIV (Detroit, MI) WJXT (Jacksonville, FL) WKMG (Orlando, FL) WSLS (Roanoke, VA)

or by calling us at (833) 971-2464.

Residents of certain jurisdictions have the right to designate an authorized agent to exercise opt-out requests on your behalf. In accordance with applicable law, we will honor such requests if you reside in one of these jurisdictions.

**_Verification Process_**

We may request that you provide additional information reasonably necessary to verify you and your consumer’s request. If you submit the request through an authorized agent, we may need to collect additional information to verify your identify before processing your request. If you are using an authorized agent to exercise your rights, we may deny a request if the authorized agent does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf.

**_Authorized Agents_**.

You may designate an authorized agent to make requests on your behalf. We will require verification that you did in fact give that person your authorization. Unless the law requires otherwise, your authorized agent must provide contact details for you. We will contact you to confirm that you authorized the agent to act on your behalf. Once you confirm, we will promptly respond to the rights request. Please note, we will not share information about a business customer with anyone not clearly affiliated with that business.

**_Response Timing_**

Upon receiving your request, we will attempt to respond within 45 days. The response period may be extended when reasonably necessary. We will inform you of any such extension within 45 days of receiving your request, together with the reason for the extension.

**_Right to Appeal_**

If we decline to take action regarding your request, we will inform you of our decision and reasoning behind it. If you wish to appeal our decision, please e-mail us at:

Select Your Station - Website Policy Email KPRC (Houston, TX) KSAT (San Antonio, TX) WDIV (Detroit, MI) WJXT / WCWJ (Jacksonville, FL) WKMG (Orlando, FL) WSLS (Roanoke, VA) Graham Media Group (Detroit, MI)

Within 60 days of receipt of an appeal, we will inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including a written explanation of the reason(s) for the decision. If your appeal is denied, you may contact your state’s Attorney General to submit a complaint related to the denial.

#### Additional Privacy Choices

In addition to the rights discussed above, there are various other ways to access, update, or limit the personal information you provide to us.

* _Account Preferences._ If you have an account on the Services, you can access and/or edit certain information you have provided to us by logging in. You may also edit your email notification practices here:

Select Your Station - Newsletter Subscriptions KPRC (Houston, TX) KSAT (San Antonio, TX) WDIV (Detroit, MI) WJXT (Jacksonville, FL) WKMG (Orlando, FL) WSLS (Roanoke, VA)

* _Additional Choices With Respect to Targeted Advertising_. As described above, we may allow third parties to compile information or aggregate statistics from our use of tracking pixels, cookies, and other tracking technologies to help them assess the effectiveness of online marketing and enable our advertisers and us to deliver targeted advertising. This allows users to see advertising more likely to be of interest to them and advertisers to send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer’s experience and the effectiveness of the ads. You can learn more about specific types of targeted advertising by visiting the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) or our [Ad Choices page](https://youradchoices.com/control). In addition to disabling cookies and other tracking technologies described above, you may opt out of receiving targeted advertising from participating ad networks, audience segment providers, ad-serving vendors, and other service providers by visiting websites operated by the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1) and [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/). Please also note that many of our websites also feature built-in cookie preference menus.

* _Global Privacy Control_. Some browsers feature a universal global privacy control (GPC) setting. You may choose to enable GPC where available. We will process a readable GPC signal as an opt-out request for targeted advertising.
    
* _Google® Analytics_. Among other technologies, the services use Google Analytics, a service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to analyze how visitors interact with the Services. [Google Analytics’s policy](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/terms/us/) describes how it collects and processes data. You can opt out of Google Analytics collection and use of data generated using the Services by going to [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
    
* _Nielsen TV Ratings_. Our properties may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, allowing you to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices, please see the [Nielsen Digital Measurement Privacy Policy](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy).
    
* _Unsubscribe from Emails_. If you have registered to receive email updates or newsletters from us, you may opt out of receiving those communications by following the “unsubscribe” instructions included in the message.
    
* _Mobile Application Users_. Due to differences between using apps and websites on mobile devices, you may need to take additional steps to disable tracking technologies in mobile apps. Many mobile devices allow you to opt out of targeted advertising for mobile apps using the settings within the mobile app or your mobile device. For more information, please check your mobile settings. You also may uninstall our apps using the standard uninstall process available on your mobile device or app marketplace.
    
* _Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms._ Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites with which the user communicates. Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, the Services currently do not act in response to these signals.

#### Other Important Information

* _No Use of Site by Children Under 13_. The Services are not directed at or intended for use by children under 13 years old. If you are under the age of 13, you should not be visiting our websites or using the Services. We do not knowingly collect or retain personal information from children under 13. If you are under the age of 13 and are visiting or otherwise using the Services, please exit immediately and do not disclose or provide any personally identifiable information to us. If you are a parent or guardian who thinks your child has disclosed information to us, please contact us so that we can remove that information from our systems.

* _Parent or Guardian Permission for Certain Minors; Acceptance of Responsibility_. If you are at least 13 years old but less than 18 years old and would like to use the Services, please ask your parent or legal guardian to review and agree to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use before you use any part of the Services. If you wish to use the Services, you must ask your parent or legal guardian for permission. Continued use of the Services indicates that you have obtained such consent; if you have not received such permission and continue to use the Services, you do so in violation of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. If you are a parent or guardian who has granted your minor permission to use the Services, you agree and understand that you are responsible for monitoring and supervising your child’s usage.
    
* _Users Outside the United States_. The Services are not directed at or intended for users outside the U.S. Please be advised that if you are located in the European Union or another region with laws related to data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, your personal information submitted through the Services and transferred to the U.S. may not have the same legal data protection as in your jurisdiction.
    
* _Retention of Personal Information_. We will retain your personal information collected through the Services for as long as we deem reasonably necessary or desirable unless any applicable law, rule, or regulation requires a different retention period. We reserve the right to delete or destroy any information collected, including personal information, at any time.
    
* _Links to Third Party Websites_. Our Services contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for other websites’ privacy practices or content. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Services and to read the privacy policies of other websites and online services.
    
* _Non-Discrimination_. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of the rights listed in this privacy policy.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update or change our privacy practices and this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we update the Privacy Policy, we will publish the revised policy on this page or as otherwise required by law. The date at the top of this page reflects the date of the most recent update. Your continued use of the Services after we make changes is deemed, to the extent allowed by law, to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

#### How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this privacy policy or the rights described above, email us at:

Select Your Station - Website Policy Email KPRC (Houston, TX) KSAT (San Antonio, TX) WDIV (Detroit, MI) WJXT / WCWJ (Jacksonville, FL) WKMG (Orlando, FL) WSLS (Roanoke, VA) Graham Media Group (Detroit, MI)

Graham Media Group, 550 W. Lafayette Blvd, Detroit, MI, 48226(313) 275-8080
